booksamillion.com 2017-10-06

# Privacy Policy : Booksamillion.com

_Last Updated: January 14, 2014_

Booksamillion.com has created this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to our customers' privacy. This document discloses our practices for gathering and disseminating information through our web site at www.booksamillion.com. 

**Information That We Collect**  
When you sign up for a Booksamillion.com account or service operated by Booksamillion.com, we store all information that you provide to us. Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitors' contact information (such as an email address) and financial information (such as account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders and information about our company to our customers. The contact information is also used to communicate with customers when necessary. Users may choose not to receive future mailings (see the CHOICE/OPT-OUT section below). The financial information that we collect is used to bill the user for products and services. 

Your IP address and browser information are stored in a "cookie" file to help identify you and your shopping cart. A cookie is a small data file that web sites write to your hard drive. A cookie cannot read data off your hard drive nor read other cookie files. You can refuse cookies by turning this option off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to purchase items from Booksamillion.com. However, cookies are needed if you wish to store items in your shopping cart between visits to the site. 

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (such as an email address). We may use this contact data to send users information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings (see the CHOICE/OPT-OUT section below). 

Any email or written correspondence that you send us may be stored. Data from any monetary transaction taking place via Booksamillion.com may be stored.

**Uses of Collected Information**  
Booksamillion.com uses collected information to enhance your experience online, authenticate you when you sign in, send notifications, fulfill your requests for services, contact you, customize the advertising or content that you see, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing**  
Booksamillion.com does not share personal information with other individuals , organizations, or companies outside of Booksamillion.com, unless we have your consent or unless:

  * We are working with trusted partners who agree to abide by the rules of this Policy and have signed a confidentiality agreement. Our site might contain links to other sites. Booksamillion.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 
  * We believe it necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

In addition, for our book clubs, online forums, customer ratings and reviews, certain personal profile information is shared with forum moderators. When you join clubs or forums, your email address and the specific information requested by particular communities will be shared with the moderators of those communities.

**Data Integrity**  
Booksamillion.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We review our data collection, storage, and process practices to ensure that we only collect, store, and process the information needed to provide our services. We depend on our users to update or correct their own personal information.

**Security and Confidentiality**  
Booksamillion.com restricts access to personal information to Booksamillion.com employees, moderators, contractors and agents who need to access the information in order to operate, sustain, improve or repair our services. These individuals are bound to confidentiality agreements and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Booksamillion.com processes orders with a SSL Secure Commerce Server which utilizes military grade encryption to protect your information. All credit card information is encoded with strong encryption before storage. Booksamillion.com does not release your credit card information or mailing address to any outside organizations without your prior electronic consent. 

**Choice/Opt Out**  
Customers may unsubscribe from a Booksamillion.com email list at any time by simply following the instructions included at the bottom of any Books-A-Million email message. 

**Contacting Booksamillion.com**  
If you wish to modify information previously provided, remove information from our database to avoid receiving future communications, or inquire about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, contact us through one of these options: 

  1. Send email to: [support@booksamillion.com](mailto:support@booksamillion.com)
  2. Send mail to:   
Customer Support, Booksamillion.com   
402 Industrial Lane, Birmingham, AL 35211 
  3. Call: 800-201-3550
